Okay so Roblox just invented the most life-changing digital economy ever.
Its literally gambling for kids.
Limiteds are rare items you can resell for Robux, sounds innocent, like digital trading cards.
But then you look at the actual system.
Items randomly go limited with zero warning.
Kids refresh the catalog at 3 AM hoping to flip a digital hat.
Theres price volatility, market manipulation, FOMO tactics.
Like I dont know what Roblox was thinking calling this collecting.
Some items cost thousands of real dollars.
The rarest one, the Dominus Empyreus, worth over 300000, for a hat that doesnt exist.
And whos trading these, children, with no regulations, no age restrictions.
Roblox really said financial literacy and meant teach kids stock market gambling.
Your 10-year-old now understands pump and dump schemes better than Wall Street.
Humanity has been saved.